[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Pretty Guardian of the City]
[الحارس الجميل للمدينة]
[Episode 24]
[الحلقة 24]
As the son of the Master of Cangyue City,
بصفته ابن سيد مدينة كانغيو ،
you should be a role model
يجب أن تكون قدوة
for the common people,
لعامة الناس ،
instead of committing a crime in the streets
بدلا من ارتكاب جريمة في الشوارع
Such an accusation
مثل هذا الاتهام
even reaches me.
حتى يصل إلي.
You're such a disgrace to
أنت مثل هذا وصمة عار
your father and I.
أنا ووالدك
It seems like it's been too long
يبدو أنه مضى وقت طويل جدًا
since I've disciplined you.
منذ أن قمت بتأديبك.
Your Ladyship.
سيدتك.
The other person provoked he first.
قام الشخص الآخر باستفزازه أولاً.
Xian'er did it
Xian'er فعل ذلك
to defend
للدفاع
the dignity of the Master's Mansion.
كرامة قصر السيد.
How dare a concubine like you
كيف تجرؤ محظية مثلك
interrupt when
عندما يقطع
Your Ladyship is speaking?
سيدتك تتحدث؟
Guards!
حراس!
Mother!
الأم!
Stop!
قف!
Mother.
الأم.
I'm the one who made the mistake.
أنا من ارتكب الخطأ.
It has nothing to do with Lady Mo.
لا علاقة له بالسيدة مو.
Just hit me.
فقط اضربني.
No, Xian'er.
لا ، Xian'er.
I offended Your Ladyship.
لقد أساءت إلى سيادتك.
I deserve to be beaten.
أنا أستحق أن أتعرض للضرب.
Your Ladyship.
سيدتك.
I admit my mistake.
أنا أعترف بخطئي.
I deserve to be beaten.
أنا أستحق أن أتعرض للضرب.
Mother!
الأم!
-I deserve to be beaten. -Mother, what are you doing?
- أستحق أن أتعرض للضرب.  -الأم ، ماذا تفعلين؟
Mother, it's not your fault.
أمي ، هذا ليس خطأك.
Mother.
الأم.
Mother!
الأم!
Mother, it's not your fault!
أمي ، هذا ليس خطأك!
Mo Yulan.
مو يولان.
Are you two putting on a show
هل أنتما الاثنان تقومان بعرض
in front of me?
امامي؟
Don't forget
لا تنسى
you're just a concubine.
أنت مجرد محظية.
You have no say
ليس لديك رأي
in the Master's Mansion.
في قصر الماجستير.
Mother.
الأم.
Lady Mo is my birth mother afterall.
السيدة مو هي والدتي بعد كل شيء.
As a mother,
كأم ،
you should understand her.
يجب أن تفهمها.
She's just anxious to protect her child.
إنها فقط حريصة على حماية طفلها.
She didn't mean to offend you.
لم تقصد الإساءة لك.
Please spare her, okay?
من فضلك اعفها ، حسنا؟
Jiang Chuxian.
جيانغ تشوكسيان.
Are you deriding me, and insinuating
هل تسخر مني وتلمح
that I don't know how to be a mother?
أنني لا أعرف كيف أكون أماً؟
I dare not do so.
لا أجرؤ على فعل ذلك.
I just...
أنا فقط...
Mo Yulan.
مو يولان.
Is this your good son?
هل هذا ابنك الصالح؟
How dare he disrespect his superior?
كيف يجرؤ على عدم احترام رئيسه؟
Today,
اليوم،
I'm going to teach you a lesson
سأعلمك درسا
and let you know
وتسمح لك الفرصة
the consequence of poor parenting.
نتيجة سوء الأبوة والأمومة.
Ansu.
أنسو.
Cut off this lowlife's hair,
اقطعوا شعر هذه الحياة المنخفضة ،
so that
لهذا السبب.
she doesn't forget her wrongdoing.
لا تنسى إثمها.
Yes.
نعم.
Mother.
الأم.
Please have mercy.
يرجى الرحمة.
I realize my mistake.
أدرك خطئي.
Mother, please have mercy!
أمي ، ارحمني من فضلك!
-No! -Mother, please have mercy!
-رقم!  -الأم ، ارحمني من فضلك!
No!
رقم!
I realize my mistake.
أدرك خطئي.
Mother.
الأم.
A lowly concubine stays a lowly concubine.
المحظية المتواضعة تبقى محظية متواضعة.
Even though you gave birth to a son for the Master,
حتى لو ولدت ابنا للسيد ،
you are still beneath me.
ما زلت تحتي.
Mother.
الأم.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
If I'm not weak and incompetent,
إذا لم أكن ضعيفًا وغير كفؤ ،
you wouldn't have been bullied like this.
لم تكن لتتعرض للتنمر من هذا القبيل.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
I came from a family of lowly status.
لقد جئت من عائلة متواضعة.
Yet, I dreamed
ومع ذلك حلمت
to be favored by the Master,
ليتم تفضيله من قبل السيد ،
and made Your Ladyship jealous.
وجعلت سيدتك تغار.
As such, you're being despised.
على هذا النحو ، أنت محتقر.
Mother.
الأم.
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
Everything I have
كل شئ عندي
is given by you.
تم إعطاؤه بواسطتك.
My Xian'er.
Xian'er بلدي.
My biggest wish
أمنيتي الكبرى
is that you can lead a normal and happy life
هو أنه يمكنك أن تعيش حياة طبيعية وسعيدة
free from disease and disaster.
خالية من الأمراض والكوارث.
I'll follow all your wishes.
سأتبع كل رغباتك.
Happy.
سعيدة.
What do you think
ما رأيك
Joy is doing with Tang Qing?
جوي تفعل مع تانغ تشينغ؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's me, Tang Qing.
إنه أنا ، تانغ تشينغ.
Give me a moment.
أعطني لحظة.
Miss Fengyi.
ملكة جمال Fengyi.
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
I'm getting changed.
أنا أتغير.
Miss Fengyi.
ملكة جمال Fengyi.
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Coming.
آت.
Tang Qing.
تانغ تشينغ.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm grounded by my father.
أنا مؤرض من والدي.
That's why, for the past two days,
لهذا السبب ، خلال اليومين الماضيين ،
I couldn't go look for you...
لم أستطع البحث عنك ...
for you all.
لكم جميعا.
Miss.
يغيب.
Is Yunxi in Xiao's Mansion?
هل Yunxi في قصر Xiao؟
You're looking for Yunxi?
هل تبحث عن Yunxi؟
Why are you
لماذا انت
looking for Yunxi here?
تبحث عن Yunxi هنا؟
Why would she be at my house?
لماذا ستكون في منزلي؟
Miss Fengyi.
ملكة جمال Fengyi.
Yunxi is missing.
Yunxi مفقود.
I can't find her anywhere.
لا أجدها في أي مكان.
Yunxi is missing?
Yunxi مفقود؟
And
و
it's likely she's been captured by your father.
من المحتمل أن والدك قد أسرها.
Miss Fengyi.
ملكة جمال Fengyi.
We need your help.
نحن نحتاج مساعدتك.
Impossible.
غير ممكن.
How could my father do such a thing?
كيف يمكن لأبي أن يفعل مثل هذا الشيء؟
Although he is a little greedy,
على الرغم من أنه جشع قليلاً ،
immoral,
عديم الاخلاق،
and overbearing,
و متعجرف
he is a good person overall.
إنه شخص جيد بشكل عام.
Absolutely impossible.
مستحيل تماما.
Tang Qing.
تانغ تشينغ.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Get up quickly.
انهض بسرعة.
Is Yunxi this important
هل Yunxi هذا مهم
to you?
لك؟
Miss,
يغيب،
I'm only alive
أنا على قيد الحياة فقط
because Yunxi saved me.
لأن Yunxi أنقذني.
Since young, I swore
منذ الصغر ، أقسمت
to protect her forever.
لحمايتها إلى الأبد.
If you are willing to help
إذا كنت على استعداد للمساعدة
find Yunxi,
تجد Yunxi ،
my life will be yours
ستكون حياتي لك
from now on.
من الان فصاعدا.
Get up first.
انهض أولا.
It's useless to beg me.
من غير المجدي أن أتوسل إلي.
My father would never kidnap Yunxi.
والدي لن يخطف Yunxi أبدًا.
He has no reason
ليس لديه سبب
to do so.
لنفعل ذلك.
We'll know if he captured Yunxi
سنعرف ما إذا كان قد أسر يونكسي
once we try to find out.
بمجرد أن نحاول معرفة ذلك.
But right now, Yunxi's life is at stake.
لكن في الوقت الحالي ، حياة يونكسي على المحك.
We can't eliminate
لا يمكننا القضاء
any possibility.
أي احتمال.
Miss Fengyi.
ملكة جمال Fengyi.
Master.
يتقن.
The people sent on the search
أرسل الناس في البحث
have found Luo Hexuan.
لقد وجدت لوه هيكسان.
But they couldn't find the white jade comb.
لكنهم لم يتمكنوا من العثور على مشط اليشم الأبيض.
Is it really as Yunxi said,
هل هو حقا كما قال يونكسي ،
that the Young Master has it?
أن السيد الشاب لديه ذلك؟
Father!
أب!
Father.
أب.
Let me out.
دعني اخرج.
I need to go to the Young Master's Mansion.
أنا بحاجة للذهاب إلى قصر يونغ ماسترز.
How many times have I told you?
كم مرة قلت لك؟
Don't spend so much time
لا تقضي الكثير من الوقت
with people from the Young Master's Mansion.
مع أشخاص من قصر يونغ ماستر.
My cousin asked someone to inform me
طلب ابن عمي من أحدهم إخباري
that they don't know
أنهم لا يعرفون
who kidnapped Yunxi.
الذي اختطف Yunxi.
She just got rescued and returned.
تم إنقاذها للتو وعادت.
She's covered in injuries.
إنها مغطاة بالإصابات.
I'm afraid she does not have much time left.
أخشى أنه لم يتبق لها الكثير من الوقت.
I have to see her one last time.
يجب أن أراها للمرة الأخيرة.
Enough.
كافية.
I told you
أخبرتك
you can't leave here.
لا يمكنك المغادرة هنا.
Go back to your room.
عد إلى غرفتك.
Father.
أب.
You can't do this...
لا يمكنك فعل هذا ...
Enough, go back to your room.
كفى ، عد إلى غرفتك.
Father, I'm angry.
أبي ، أنا غاضب.
[Xiao's Mansion]
[قصر شياو]
Steward.
ستيوارد.
Please find a doctor
من فضلك ابحث عن طبيب
for Yunxi.
لـ Yunxi.
She's dying.
إنها تحتضر.
I beg...
أنا حقيبة ...
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
You have no right to speak.
ليس لديك الحق في الكلام.
Bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Someone broke in.
اقتحم شخص ما.
We fell into a trap.
وقعنا في الفخ.
You. Bring some men to stop them.
أنت.  اجلب بعض الرجال لمنعهم.
You must not let them in.
يجب ألا تسمح لهم بالدخول.
Yes.
نعم.
You. Take Yunxi
أنت. خذ Yunxi
and follow me through the back door.
واتبعني من الباب الخلفي.
Okay.
تمام.
Hurry.
عجل.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Qing.
تشينغ.
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Don't come over.
لا تأتي.
I'll kill her if you come closer.
سأقتلها إذا اقتربت.
Let her go
اسمح لها أن تذهب
and I'll spare your life.
وسأحافظ على حياتك.
If you dare to hurt her even the slightest,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على إيذائها حتى ولو طفيفًا ،
I'll make you regret
سوف تجعلك تندم
being here.
الوجود هنا.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Why are you so stubborn?
لماذا أنت عنيد جدا؟
You can exchange this woman
يمكنك تبادل هذه المرأة
for the greatest power in Cangyue City.
لأعظم قوة في مدينة كانغيو.
Isn't that good?
أليس هذا جيد؟
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
I'm afraid I can't.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع.
I'm just following orders.
أنا فقط أتبع الأوامر.
This woman is coming with me.
هذه المرأة قادمة معي.
Pepper.
فلفل.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
You...
أنت...
Go!
يذهب!
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Pepper!
فلفل!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You can't kill me.
لا يمكنك قتلي.
-I'm Commander Xiao's... -You old man!
- أنا القائد شياو ... - أنت رجل عجوز!
Commander Xiao's man.
رجل القائد شياو.
Pepper.
فلفل.
Yunxi.
يونشى.
-Pepper. -Yunxi.
-فلفل.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Yunxi!
يونشى!
Wake up, Yunxi.
استيقظ ، Yunxi.
Wake up!
استيقظ!
Doctor, how is she?
دكتور كيف حالها؟
When will she wake up?
متى تستيقظ؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
The lady already has incurable poison
السيدة لديها بالفعل سم غير قابل للشفاء
in her body.
في جسدها.
Now, she's even suffered
الآن ، حتى أنها عانت
such inhumane torture.
مثل هذا التعذيب اللاإنساني.
Her body is weak beyond salvage.
جسدها ضعيف لا يمكن إنقاذه.
At most, she has
على الأكثر ، لديها
about a month to live.
حوالي شهر للعيش.
You quack!
أنت الدجال!
What nonsense is that?
ما هذا الهراء؟
How could she die?
كيف يمكن أن تموت؟
I'll go find my third brother.
سأذهب لأجد أخي الثالث.
He has excellent medical skills.
لديه مهارات طبية ممتازة.
He must know a way to save Yunxi.
يجب أن يعرف طريقة لإنقاذ Yunxi.
No need to go.
لا حاجة للذهاب.
What the doctor said is true.
ما قاله الطبيب صحيح.
Yunxi has the poison of heartburn
Yunxi لديه سم الحموضة المعوية
before her birth.
قبل ولادتها.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
she has been suppressing the poison with poison.
لقد كانت تقوم بقمع السم بالسم.
But now, even poison
ولكن الآن ، حتى السم
can't suppress the poison of heartburn.
لا تستطيع قمع سم الحموضة المعوية.
She has just been
كانت هنا
putting up a brave front.
وضع جبهة شجاعة.
♫Luckily, my heart remains the same when all the flowers fall♫
♫ لحسن الحظ ، يظل قلبي كما هو عندما تسقط كل الأزهار
♫I've been waiting for you for a thousand years♫
♫ أنا في انتظارك منذ ألف عام ♫
♫Dream that we are on the old road we met♫
♫ احلم أننا على الطريق القديم الذي التقينا به
Impossible.
غير ممكن.
♫See you gently play the zither♫
♫ أراك تعزف آلة القانون برفق
She promised me
لقد وعدتني
to elope with me.
للهروب معي.
♫Who are you waiting for to make you a pot of tea?♫
♫ من الذي تنتظره ليصنع لك إبريق شاي؟
We will build a small city,
سنبني مدينة صغيرة ،
spend our days together,
نقضي أيامنا معًا ،
and grow old together.
ونكبر معًا.
How could she die?
كيف يمكن أن تموت؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Yunxi didn't want to accept
لم يرغب Yunxi في القبول
your feelings.
مشاعرك.
But she fell deeply in love with you.
لكنها وقعت في حبك بعمق.
When you mistakenly thought
عندما اعتقدت خطأ
that she fell in love with someone else,
أنها وقعت في حب شخص آخر ،
she took the chance to leave you.
انتهزت الفرصة لتركك.
This way,
من هنا،
you won't suffer
لن تعاني
from your yearning for her.
من اشتياقك إليها.
♫Count the sorrows, who help each other in straits with feeble strength?♫
عد الأحزان ، من يساعدون بعضهم البعض في الضيق بقوة ضعيفة؟
♫There will be a pure place to expel the karma♫
سيكون هناك مكان طاهر لطرد الكارما
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Why are you so silly?
لماذا أنت سخيف جدا؟
♫Unexpectedly, not until the pomp ended♫
♫ بشكل غير متوقع ، ليس حتى انتهى البهاء ♫
♫Can I understand the unforgettable feeling♫
♫ هل أستطيع أن أفهم الشعور الذي لا يُنسى
No matter what you do to me,
لا يهم ما تفعله بي ،
I will never forget you.
لن أنساك أبدا.
♫The hair has been grey, while the destiny can't be seen through♫
♫ كان الشعر رمادي بينما القدر لا يمكن رؤيته من خلال ♫
You can't leave me.
لا يمكنك أن تتركني.
♫Luckily, my heart remains the same when all the flowers fall♫
♫ لحسن الحظ ، يظل قلبي كما هو عندما تسقط كل الأزهار
You can't abandon me.
لا يمكنك التخلي عني.
♫I've been waiting for you for a thousand years♫
♫ أنا في انتظارك منذ ألف عام ♫
♫Dream that we are on the old road we met♫
♫ احلم أننا على الطريق القديم الذي التقينا به
No matter what, I'll find the Fengchi antidote.
بغض النظر عن ماذا ، سأجد ترياق Fengchi.
♫See you gently play the zither♫
♫ أراك تعزف آلة القانون برفق
At all cost,
بأي ثمن ،
♫Who are you waiting for to make you a pot of tea?♫
♫ من الذي تنتظره ليصنع لك إبريق شاي؟
I will cure you.
سوف أعالجك.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Jiang Chaoxi.
جيانغ تشوكسي.
How dare you kill my men?
كيف تجرؤ على قتل رجالي؟
For as long as my name is Xiao Huasheng,
طالما أن اسمي شياو هواشنغ ،
I will see that you be killed.
سأرى أنك ستقتل.
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
Does it still hurt?
هل ما زال يؤلم؟
Silly.
سخيف.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
لماذا لم تخبرني في وقت سابق؟
You thought you were smart
كنت تعتقد أنك ذكي
to leave me.
لتتركني.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Actually, deep down, I've always known
في الواقع ، في أعماقي ، كنت أعرف دائمًا
that I'm not a good match for you.
أنني لست مناسبًا لك.
But I still want to
لكن ما زلت أريد ذلك
be with you forever.
ابقى معك الى الابد.
I want too much.
اريد الكثير.
Yes.
نعم.
You want too much.
أنت تريد الكثير.
You even want to
أنت حتى تريد
leave me.
أتركني.
But you don't know
لكنك لا تعرف
that I want more.
اريد المزيد.
I want to be with you
أريد أن أكون معك
for every moment.
لكل لحظة.
I want to be with you forever,
أريد أن أكون معك للأبد،
in life and in death.
في الحياة والموت.
No.
رقم.
I don't want to be with you forever.
لا أريد أن أكون معك إلى الأبد.
I don't want you to be with me in life and in death.
لا أريدك أن تكون معي في الحياة والموت.
I just want you to live well.
أنا فقط أريدك أن تعيش بشكل جيد.
If you're not by my side,
إذا لم تكن بجانبي ،
what's the point in living?
ما الفائدة من العيش؟
Promise me
اوعدني
you will try your best to stay alive.
ستبذل قصارى جهدك للبقاء على قيد الحياة.
I will find the Fengchi antidote
سوف أجد ترياق Fengchi
and cure you.
وعلاجك.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
I'm not exactly in the position to say this.
أنا لست بالضبط في وضع يسمح لي بقول هذا.
But Hexuan is in a coma,
لكن Hexuan في غيبوبة ،
so I'm akin to Yunxi's real brother.
لذلك أنا أقرب إلى شقيق يونكسي الحقيقي.
As her brother,
بصفتها شقيقها ،
I have to ask you.
ينبغي أن أسألك.
How do you treat your relationship with Yunxi?
كيف تتعامل مع علاقتك بـ Yunxi؟
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
you have accepted the royal engagement.
لقد قبلت الخطبة الملكية.
Although she can't live much longer,
على الرغم من أنها لا تستطيع العيش لفترة أطول ،
I won't allow you
لن اسمح لك
to treat her without respect.
لمعاملتها دون احترام.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
My wife
زوجتي
can't be anyone else.
لا يمكن أن يكون أي شخص آخر.
It must be Yunxi.
يجب أن يكون Yunxi.
As for the engagement,
أما بالنسبة للخطوبة ،
I'll find a way to refuse.
سأجد طريقة للرفض.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
By the way,
على فكرة،
can Fengchi really
يمكن فنغتشي حقا
save Yunxi?
حفظ يونشى؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
It was developed by the Ghost Doctor
تم تطويره بواسطة Ghost Doctor
with great efforts.
بجهود كبيرة.
If it doesn't work,
إذا لم ينجح الأمر ،
there will be no other cure
لن يكون هناك علاج آخر
in this world.
في هذا العالم.
However,
لكن،
even if we find Fengchi,
حتى لو وجدنا Fengchi ،
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
you'll have to make a choice.
عليك أن تختار.
After all, Yunxi's biggest wish
بعد كل شيء ، أمنية يونكسي الأكبر
is to wake her brother up.
هو إيقاظ أخيها.
Even if she will hate me,
حتى لو كانت تكرهني ،
I only have one option.
لدي خيار واحد فقط.
Hexuan will do the same.
ستفعل Hexuan نفس الشيء.
And
و
I always respect his decision.
أنا دائما أحترم قراره.
Now that you've completely offended
الآن بعد أن أساءت تمامًا
Xiao Huasheng
شياو هوا شنغ
and killed his trusted subordinate,
وقتل المرؤوس الموثوق به ،
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
he won't let you off easily.
لن يسمح لك بالخروج بسهولة.
Even without this conflict,
حتى بدون هذا الصراع ،
the feigned cordiality between my uncle and I
الود الوهمي بيني وبين عمي
won't last long.
لن تدوم طويلا.
We have to end it.
علينا أن ننهيها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't let him
لن أسمح له
hurt Yunxi again.
تؤذي Yunxi مرة أخرى.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I will protect Yunxi.
سأحمي Yunxi.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
Lady Mo has passed away.
السيدة مو قد توفيت.
Greetings, father and mother.
تحياتي الأب والأم.
Chuxian,
تشوشيان ،
I'm sorry for your loss.
آسف على خسارتك.
I didn't expect that
لم أتوقع ذلك
she would take things so hard.
كانت ستأخذ الأمور بصعوبة شديدة.
Yesterday, as the Lady of Cangyue City,
أمس ، بصفتها سيدة مدينة كانغيو ،
I scolded
وبخت
Xian'er.
Xian'er.
Because Lady Mo contradicted me many times,
لأن السيدة مو ناقضتني عدة مرات ،
I punished her.
أنا عاقبتها.
If I knew
لو كنت اعلم
she would do such a silly thing,
كانت ستفعل مثل هذا الشيء السخيف ،
I would not have dared to
لم أكن لأجرؤ على ذلك
reprimand her.
توبيخها.
Forget it. Everyone has his own fate.
انسى ذلك.  كل شخص له مصيره.
Just arrange her funeral.
فقط رتب جنازتها.
As for my mother's burial,
أما بالنسبة لدفن أمي ،
there is no need to bother
لا داعي للعناء
father and Your Ladyship.
والدك وسيادتك.
Before her death,
قبل وفاتها
I was the only one
كنت الوحيد
close to her.
على مقربة منها.
I will arrange
سوف أرتب
her funeral properly.
جنازتها بشكل صحيح.
Xian'er.
Xian'er.
Come back, Xian'er!
تعال يا Xian'er!
Xian'er!
Xian'er!
This is ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
He doesn't
لا يفعل
regard me with any respect.
بالنسبة لي مع أي احترام.
Father. Mother.
أب.  الأم.
After all, Chuxian just lost his birth mother.
بعد كل شيء ، فقد Chuxian للتو والدته.
He is too grieved
إنه حزين للغاية
to control his behavior.
للسيطرة على سلوكه.
It can be excused.
يمكن أن يكون معذور.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
I'll go check on him now.
سأذهب للتحقق منه الآن.
[The Tomb of Mother Mo Yulan]
[قبر الأم مو يولان]
Mother, I'm sorry.
أمي ، أنا آسف.
I have failed to protect you.
لقد فشلت في حمايتك.
Third brother,
الأخ الثالث ،
I'm sorry for your loss.
آسف على خسارتك.
It's my fault for not protecting you.
إنه خطأي لعدم حمايتك.
My mother ended up like this
انتهى الأمر بوالدتي على هذا النحو
because of that so-called good Lady.
بسبب ما يسمى بالسيدة الطيبة.
I must defeat Xiao Huasheng.
لا بد لي من هزيمة شياو هواشنغ.
That damned pest.
تلك الآفة اللعينة.
We are brothers.
نحن اخوة.
I'll be by your side.
ساكون بجانبك.
Stay with him.
البقاء معه.
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
he'd been through
لقد مر به
so much.
كثيرا.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
I should have
يجب ان احصل
cared more about him.
اهتم به أكثر.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Dr. Xian just
الدكتور زيان فقط
lost his mother.
فقد والدته.
It's inevitable for him to feel sad.
لا مفر منه أن يشعر بالحزن.
Without me,
من دوني،
his fate might have been
ربما كان مصيره
completely different.
مختلف تماما.
I owe him.
انا أدين له.
It's time
حان الوقت
to give everything back to him.
لنعيد كل شيء إليه.
How dare you break off the engagement?
كيف تجرؤ على فسخ الخطوبة؟
Do you really treat my order
هل حقا تعامل طلبي
as a joke?
على سبيل المزاح؟
That's impossible!
هذا مستحيل!
I'd rather give up
أفضل الاستسلام
the position of Young Master.
منصب السيد الشاب.
If you continue to push me,
إذا واصلت دفعني ،
I would rather die.
أفضل الموت.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
I'm unfilial.
أنا غير متحفظ.
Please grant my wish.
من فضلك أعط أمنيتي.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll grant your wish.
سأمنح أمنيتك.
Guards!
حراس!
Drag him out.
اسحبه للخارج.
Give him a hard beating!
أعطه ضربة قاسية!
Go on!
تابع!
Stop!
قف!
Stop beating him!
توقفوا عن ضربه!
Do you want to kill
هل تريد أن تقتل
our son?
ابننا؟
Ask him.
اسأله.
In order to break off the engagement,
من أجل فسخ الخطوبة ،
your perfect son is even giving up
حتى أن ابنك المثالي يستسلم
his position as the Young Master.
منصبه بصفته السيد الشاب.
Xi'er.
شي.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Apologize to your father.
اعتذر لوالدك.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
I've made up my mind.
أنا إتخذت قراري.
I'm at your disposal.
أنا تحت تصرفك.
You...
أنت...
Xi'er.
شي.
Fine.
بخير.
Since you are so determined,
بما أنك مصمم على هذا النحو ،
I'll do as you wish.
سأفعل ما يحلو لك.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you are no longer
انت لست طويل
the Young Master of Cangyue City.
السيد الشاب لمدينة كانغيو.
You are grounded to reflect,
أنت متأصل في التفكير ،
and not allowed to go out again.
ولا يسمح لها بالخروج مرة أخرى.
Please think twice, Master.
من فضلك فكر مرتين يا معلمة.
He is just muddleheaded.
هو مجرد مشوش الذهن.
Xi'er.
شي.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Didn't you agree to
لم توافق على
the engagement?
الخطوبة؟
Here.
هنا.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Why are you going back on your word?
لماذا تتراجع عن كلمتك؟
Now you've even lost
لقد خسرت الآن
your place as the Young Master.
مكانك بصفتك السيد الشاب.
Mother,
الأم،
did you meet Yunxi?
هل قابلت يونكسي؟
What did you say to her?
ماذا كنت أقول لها؟
All this for her?
كل هذا لها؟
I didn't expect you'd disobey your parents
لم أتوقع أن تعصي والديك
for a woman.
لامرأة.
Mother.
الأم.
No matter what you will do,
بغض النظر عما ستفعله ،
I will never leave her
لن اتركها ابدا
or marry someone else.
أو الزواج من شخص آخر.
So you don't even want to
لذلك أنت لا تريد حتى ذلك
be the Young Master?
كن السيد الشاب؟
Your uncle is right.
عمك على حق.
You're really stubborn.
أنت حقًا عنيد.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
it didn't work out in the way
لم ينجح الأمر في الطريق
you and uncle had planned.
كنت قد خططت أنت وعمك.
What?
ماذا؟
All this time,
كل هذا الوقت،
you've been trying to make me
كنت تحاول أن تجعلني
a puppet of the Xiao family
دمية لعائلة شياو
to control the whole Cangyue City.
للسيطرة على مدينة كانغيو بأكملها.
Mother.
الأم.
Jiang Chaoxi!
جيانغ شاوكسي!
You should know
يجب ان تعرف
what power means to us.
ماذا تعني القوة بالنسبة لنا.
To you,
لك،
power is everything.
القوة هي كل شيء.
But to me,
ولكن بالنسبة لي،
it is nothing.
إنه لا شيء.
Now,
حاليا،
I have found
لقد وجدت
the most precious thing.
أغلى شيء.
If you dare marry her,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على الزواج منها ،
you would not be allowed to call me mother again.
لن يسمح لك بالاتصال بي أمي مرة أخرى.
Why are you so foolish?
لماذا أنت بهذا الغباء؟
Master will never
سيد لن أبدا
allow you to break off the engagement.
تسمح لك بقطع الخطوبة.
Just accept it first.
فقط اقبله أولا.
Who says I'm foolish?
من يقول أنني أحمق؟
Although I was beaten,
على الرغم من أنني تعرضت للضرب ،
I receive your concern.
أتلقى قلقك.
It's worth it.
انه يستحق ذلك.
I'm no longer the Young Master.
أنا لم أعد السيد الشاب.
I'm just your Jiang Chaoxi now.
أنا فقط جيانغ تشوكسي الخاص بك الآن.
You can't abandon me.
لا يمكنك التخلي عني.
But since you broke off the engagement
لكن منذ أن قطعت الخطوبة
and can't be the Young Master,
ولا يمكن أن يكون السيد الشاب ،
you're no longer valuable for exploit
لم تعد ذا قيمة للاستغلال
to Xiao Huasheng.
إلى Xiao Huasheng.
I'm afraid he'll harm you.
أخشى أن يؤذيك.
Don't worry about that.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
I know how to deal with it.
أعرف كيف أتعامل معها.
The most important thing now
أهم شيء الآن
is to take care of yourself.
هو الاعتناء بنفسك.
And...
و...
And what?
و ماذا؟
And marry me
وتزوجني
and have children for me.
ولدي أطفال.
What's wrong? You don't want to?
ما هو الخطأ؟  لا تريد؟
No,
رقم،
I want to.
أريد أن.
Yunxi,
يونشى ،
you must live on
يجب أن تعيش
and live a long life.
وتعيش حياة طويلة.
We still have many things
لا يزال لدينا الكثير من الأشياء
to do.
لكى يفعل.
Live on and stay well.
عش وابقى بصحة جيدة
Miss.
يغيب.
Something happened.
شيء ما حصل.
Young Master broke off the engagement
قطع السيد الشاب الخطوبة
and was deposed
وتم خلعه
as the Young Master.
بصفته السيد الشاب.
He dislikes me so much.
يكرهني كثيرا.
he would rather ruin his future
يفضل تدمير مستقبله
than marry me.
من الزواج بي.
Your visit
زيارتك
today
اليوم
makes me
يجعلني
very happy.
سعيد جدا.
I should have come earlier.
كان يجب أن آتي في وقت سابق.
It was rude of me
كان وقحا مني
to distance you before.
ليبعدك من قبل.
I've been there before.
قد كنت هناك قبلا.
I've seen so many people.
لقد رأيت الكثير من الناس.
So I understand
لذلك أنا أفهم
what you're thinking about.
بما تفكر فيه.
Life
حياة
is like the green tea
مثل الشاي الأخضر
in this teacup,
في هذا فنجان الشاي ،
with ups
مع يو بي إس
and downs.
والهبوط.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
As the son of the Master,
بصفته ابن السيد ،
my brother grew up
نشأ أخي
with everything he wanted.
مع كل ما يريد.
As a concubine's son,
كإبن محظية ،
I would never get any attention
لن أحظى بأي اهتمام
no matter how much I compromised.
بغض النظر عن مقدار المساومة.
Like the tea leaves that have sinked,
مثل أوراق الشاي التي غرقت ،
with no way to come up.
مع عدم وجود طريقة للخروج.
Judging from what you said,
انطلاقا مما قلته ،
you must have your own plan.
يجب أن يكون لديك خطتك الخاصة.
Uncle asked me to come more often.
طلب مني العم أن آتي في كثير من الأحيان.
You must have
يجب أن تمتلك
some expectations of me.
بعض التوقعات مني.
Smart.
ذكي.
You're worthy to be taught.
أنت تستحق أن تتعلم.
Unlike Xi'er
على عكس شي
who is stubborn
من هو العنيد
and useless.
وغير مجدية.
As brother expected,
كما توقع أخي ،
Xiao Huasheng really took the bait.
لقد أخذ شياو هوا شنغ الطُعم حقًا.
You really deserve
أنت حقا تستحق
to be taught carefully.
ليتم تدريسها بعناية.
If so,
لو ذلك،
just like these tea leaves,
تمامًا مثل أوراق الشاي هذه ،
you will come out on top one day.
سوف تخرج في القمة ذات يوم.
What you said
ماذا قلت
is what I want.
هو ما اريد.
It's good for you
انه جيد لك
to have this ambition to change your fate.
أن يكون لديك هذا الطموح لتغيير مصيرك.
Why don't we get rid of Jiang Chaoxi first?
لماذا لا نتخلص من Jiang Chaoxi أولاً؟
If we are on the same side in the future,
إذا كنا في نفس الجانب في المستقبل ،
I will do my best
سأبذل قصارى جهدي
to help you get what you want.
لمساعدتك في الحصول على ما تريد.
I will always remember your help.
سأتذكر دائما مساعدتك.
Okay.
تمام.
That's what I want to hear.
هذا ما أريد أن أسمعه.
Sit down.
اجلس.
I know
أنا أعرف
you like the girl from the Nangong family.
تحب الفتاة من عائلة Nangong.
But I also heard that
لكنني سمعت ذلك أيضًا
she is born physically weak.
ولدت ضعيفة جسديا.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
I guess she can't help you
أعتقد أنها لا تستطيع مساعدتك
run the mansion.
إدارة القصر.
Look.
نظرة.
Your cousin, Fengyi,
ابن عمك ، Fengyi ،
is different.
مختلف.
She is healthy
انها صحية
and intelligent.
وذكي.
And some say
ويقول البعض
she is born blessed.
ولدت مباركا.
I...
أنا...
Fengyi
فنجي
is really healthy.
هو حقا صحي.
You...
أنت...
Yes.
نعم.
Help!
مساعدة!
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Look at her.
انظر إليها.
A lively girl
فتاة مفعمة بالحيوية
with a loud voice.
بصوت عال.
You two. One is quiet. One is chirpy.
أنت أيضا.  واحد هادئ.  واحد هو مرح.
What a perfect match.
يا لها من تطابق مثالي.
I'm sure you two
أنا متأكد من أنكما الاثنان
will have fun together.
سيستمتعون معًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Fun.
مرح.
Xian'er.
Xian'er.
We are
نحن
family.
الأسرة.
If you two can be together,
إذا كان بإمكانك أن تكونا معًا ،
we'll get closer.
سنقترب.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟